Has this ever happened to you?
It's five o'clock, you have to be at a party at six o'clock and you still have your gift to wrap.
What are you going to do?
Well I can help.
I'm Janet Casto, your Independent Demonstrator with Stampin' Up, and I'm going to show you a quick and easy way using a gift bag and tissue paper to really create a beautiful gift wrapping.
So I had already stamped on this gift bag and so I've done that and just tied a little ribbon as an accent.
And now I want to work with my tissue.
So what I'm going to do is insert my ink and put my wheel in.
And when I'm putting my tissue paper in, the only thing that's going to show is the top edges, so that's the only thing I really need to stamp.
And I'm just going to go ahead and run a couple lines.
And this coordinates beautifully with the design on my gift bag.
So you're going to go ahead and do that a couple times.
And I'm going to do it on both sides because I like to spread my tissue paper out once I put my gift in.
You could use an edge, a straight edge if you needed to.
I like to just eyeball it.
So once that's done, I'm going to take my gift and I'm going to my friend's birthday party so I have made her a mug with some rub ons that says friends.
So I'm going to put that in the middle of my tissue paper, pull all my edges up, first I'm going to flip it around, there we go, pull all my edges up, put it into my gift bag, and then I'm going to fluff it up so she will see the beautiful stamping I did with my wheel on her gift.
So you have a quick and easy gift wrap, your tissue paper looks beautiful, she'll thing you spent a million bucks on it.
I'm Janet Casto your Independent Demonstrator with Stampin' Up.
Don't be late for your next party.